hey welcome to this quick demo of spring
嘿，欢迎来到这个 Spring 的快速演示
boot and spring loaded so I have an STS
靴子和Spring 加载，所以我有一个STS
here I'm gonna use a spring starter
在这里我要用一个Spring 起动器
project wizard which talks to the
与项目对话的项目向导
initializer wrap I'm gonna make this a
初始化包装，我要做一个
new using the web starter create the app
使用Web Starter创建新应用
and be an app that it's just gonna run
成为一个可以运行的应用程序
that using the built-in launch and we
使用内置的发射，我们
have new tabs
有新标签
just checking that's behaving that also
只是检查它的行为
creates a launch configuration that I'm
创建我正在的启动配置
going to edit in a minute I'm into this
待会儿我要编辑
app I'm gonna add a new controller
应用我要添加一个新的控制器
tralala configuration gonna ride a
tralala配置将骑
simple request mapping
简单请求映射
sorry
抱歉
so that's all bad I'm gonna run it but
所以这很糟糕，我要运行它，但是
this time I've been a turn-on
这次我已经开机
spring-loaded so all I do is pass in a
Spring 式的，所以我要做的只是传递一个
shelter agent and turn off the verify
庇护代理并关闭验证
don't panic now there's nothing SDSU's
现在不要惊慌，没有SDSU
hear about the reloading that's going on
听到正在进行的重新加载
spring loaded runs entirely
Spring 加载完全运行
independently Artfest yes just it's
独立Artfest是的，只是
easier to show you inside sts from a
更容易向您展示内部sts
demo Pont of view so now the apps being
演示视图的Pont，所以现在应用程序正在
modified at startup so it can be changed
在启动时进行了修改，因此可以对其进行更改
here runtime the apps running looks
在这里运行时，正在运行的应用看起来
check-in points there yep same plan
那里的入住点是相同的计划
points there and reads three motors in
指向那里并读取三个电机
mix so I can edit my up without
混合，这样我就可以编辑我的
restarting
重新开始
it's tearing show method refactoring
令人眼花show乱的show方法重构
so this create a new method on the fly
这样就可以动态创建一个新方法
show you're doing something different
表明你在做不同的事情
yeah so that's all working I can add
是的，这样就可以了，我可以添加
another request mapping
另一个请求映射
so happy and we started again so the
很高兴，我们又开始了，所以
older ones there but actually the new
那里比较老，但实际上是新的
point is there and it supported a
点在那里，它支持一个
request power arm it's passed that in
请求动力臂通过了
it's working I can change this binding
它正在工作，我可以更改此绑定
for the request per am there you go
对于那里的请求，您去
I can carry on adding more methods or
我可以继续添加更多方法，或者
more handlers change those handlers all
更多处理程序将这些处理程序全部更改
the annotations add them and remove them
批注添加它们并将其删除
all without restarting the app all
全部而无需重新启动所有应用
because of what spring-loaded to doing
因为 Spring 要做的事
in other colors there are restrictions
其他颜色有限制
but covering those would be boring I
但是覆盖那些会很无聊
just wanted to show the cool stuff
只是想展示很酷的东西